Parisa Razzaghi

Master's student in Interactive Media Technology

Stockholm, Sweden linkedin.com/in/parisraz parisdesign.github.io paris.razzaghi@gmail.com +46708283753

I am a student deeply interested in improving human-technology interactions and creating innovative designs. I previously graduated in the top 10 percent of my class in computer engineering and am currently pursuing my master's degree at KTH while also serving as a student ambassador. With experience as a system support specialist, teacher assistant, and UI/UX designer, my goal is to bridge the gap between design and implementation while continuously enhancing my knowledge in these areas.

Work Experience -

Student Ambassador

KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Oct 2022 - Current

- Answering questions and guiding students.
- Providing information for visitors on campus tours.
- Participating in webinars and video content.

 $\textbf{Skills:} \ \mathsf{Communication} \cdot \mathsf{Planning} \cdot \mathsf{Perception} \cdot \mathsf{Socializing}$

UI/UX Designer Freelancer Jun 2020 - Jul 2021

• Designing applications and websites for practice and clients.

Skills: UI/UX · Adobe XD · Figma · Photography

Teacher Assistant Alzahra University Sep 2017 - Sep 2019

- Holding exercise-solving classes for 60 students each semester.
- Creating lesson plans, taking tests, and helping with grading the students.
- Explaining hard-to-understand exercises via video guides.

Skills: Planning · Problem-solving · Communication · Adaptability

System Support Specialist Alzahra University

Aug 2018 - Aug 2020

- Assisting teachers and students using Al-Zahra University's virtual learning environment.
- Fixing and searching for solutions regarding problems that occurred for users while using Adobe Connect and LMS.
- Making visual guides for users.

Skills: Adobe Connect · Moodle · Video Editing · Problem-solving · Communication

Education ——

Bachelors degree, Computer Engineering

Alzahra University

2016 - 2020

Master's degree, Interactive Media Technology

KTH Royal Institute of Technology

Aug 2022 - Current

Languages -

English Professional Working Proficiency

Persian Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Japanese Limited Working Proficiency